Preliminary Guide to the Takey Crist Papers, 1944-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession, 2004 (2004-0098), 27 Boxes
  - UNC Subject Files Series
    - Speech - 1972, Oct. 4, Western Carolina University, Cullowhee, N.C. (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Oct. 6, NC Superintendents and Principals Meeting (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Oct. 13, Butner Symposium (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Oct. 17, NCSU Agricultural Extension Service, Tarboro Conference (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Oct. 27, Jacksonville, N.C., NCSSA Southeastern Meeting (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Nov. 1-3, NC Conference on Public Nursing (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Nov. 4, N.C. Medical Assistants (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Nov. 9-10, Univ. of S.D. Vermillion, SD (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Nov. 14, Westminster College, New Wilmington, PA (Box 25)
    - Speech - 1972, Nov. 15, School of Public Health, Course 100 (Box 25)
    - Speech - Fort Bragg, SUI (Box 25)
    - Speeches - Miscellaneous (Box 25)
    - Speech - Premarital Intercourse on the Increase (Box 25)
    - Statistics for Onslow County (Box 25)
    - Sterilization (Box 26)
    - Sterilization, 1973-1974 (Box 26)
    - Sterilization for eugenic purposes (Box 26)
    - Stress Incontinence in UNC Coeds (Box 26)
    - Sterilizations in Young People, 1971 (Box 26)
    - Stress Urinary Incontinence (Box 26)
    - Suicides (Box 26)
    - Tace Drug Study (Box 26)
    - Tace 2nd 48 (Box 26)
    - Tragedies of the Sexual Revolution (Box 26)
    - Ulcers - Newborn and Younger Age Group (Box 26)
    - UNC-Infirmary (Box 26)
    - UNC-Infirmary, 1966-1967 (Box 26)
    - UNC - Open House (Box 26)
    - Uterine Corpus (Box 26)
    - Venereal Disease (Box 26)
    - Venereal Disease - HEW (Box 27)
    - Venereal Disease - Study by Lloyd Comstock (Box 27)
    - Venereal Disease - Studies (Box 27)
    - Vaginal Sprays (Box 27)
    - Women and Gynecologists (Box 27)
    - Women's Liberation (Box 27)
    - W.W. Norton and Company (Box 27)
    - Zero Population Growth (Box 27)
    - Printed and published materials
      - Richard Mier et al., Elephants and Butterflies…and Contraceptives, ECOS, 1970, 3rd edition 1971 (Box 27)
      - Duke Committee on Contraception and Abortion, A Guide to Contraception and Abortion, 1971 edition (Box 27)
      - Nancy Crampton, Between Your Navel and Your Knees, University of Houston Student Association, 1972 (Box 27)
      - James L. Burks et al., Beyond Eros, University of Chicago, 1971 (Box 27)
      - Elaine C. Pierson, Sex is Never An Emergency, Philadelphia, J.B. Lippincott Company, 1970, 2nd edition 1971 (Box 27)
      - Student Health Service, On Either Side of the Mushroom, UNC, 1971 (Box 27)
        A booklet about drugs and drug use
      - Kenneth Jones et al., Sex Information, Student Government and the Division of Student Affairs, NC State University, 1969, 2 copies (Box 27)
      - What we know about Drugs, NC State Univ., Student Government, 1970-1971 (Box 27)
      - Student Committee on Human Sexuality, Sex and the Yale Student, 1970 (Box 27)
      - James Trussell and Steve Chandler, The Loving Book, Charlotte: Red Clay Publishers, 1971 (Box 27)
      - Winifred Kempton, Techniques for Leading Group Discussions on Human Sexuality (Planned Parenthood of Southeastern PA, 1972, 3rd printing 1975) (Box 27)
      - Wayne Middendorf and Bruce Middendorf, A Sperm and Egg Handbook for buffalo students (SUNY Univ. Press, 1971) (Box 27)
      - (Planned Parenthood of Southeastern PA, 1972, 3rd printing 1975) (Box 27)
      - Wayne Middendorf and Bruce Middendorf, A Sperm and Egg Handbook (SUNY Univ. Press, 1973) (Box 27)
      - Richard Mier et al., Amor Con Tranquilidad (Mexico 1972) (Box 27)
        Translation of Elephants and Butterflies
      - Elaine P. Mastroianni, A Guide for University of Pennsylvania Students 1970-1971 (U of PA, 1970) (Box 27)
      - Human Sexuality Update 1, no. 1 (Spring 1980) (Box 27)
        Current journal articles in sex and sexuality
      - Marian Johnson Gray and Roger W. Gray, How To Take the Worry Out of Being Close: An Egg and Sperm Handbook (Oakland CA, 1971) (Box 27)
      - Larry M. Lance, Population and Human Sexuality (Institute for Urban Studies and Community Service, UNC Charlotte, 1973) (Box 27)
        Collection of papers from 1972 Population Workshop. Includes two papers by Takey on contraception and abortion
      - American University Hotline, The Ups and Downs of Drug Use (Spring 1973) (Box 27)
      - American University Hotline, Sex Facts for the AU Student (Fall 1973) (Box 27)
      - Lynn K. Hansen et al., How to Have Intercourse Without Getting Screwed (ASUW Women's Commission, Jan. 1972) (Box 27)
      - Lynn K. Hansen et al., How to Have Intercourse Without Getting Screwed (ASUW Women's Commission, June 1971) (Box 27)
      - Robert E. Hall, Sex and Marriage (PPWP, 1965) (Box 27)
      - Linda Thurston, Birth Control, Abortion, and Venereal Disease: A Guide for the Boston University Student (Boston Univ. Student Union, 1969-70) (Box 27)
      - Sol Gordon, Ten Heavy Facts About Sex (Syracuse University, 1971) (Box 27)
      - Sol Gordon, Capt. Veedee-o and Ms. Wanda Lust in VD Claptrap, Ed-U Press, 1972 (Box 27)
      - Journal of the American College Health Association 19, no. 3 (Feb. 1971) (Box 27)
        Includes an article on student use of drugs
      - David B. Van Vleck, How and Why Not to have that baby, Optimum Population, 1971 (Box 27)
        Much of the E&B material is from here
      - Birth Control Handbook, McGill University, 1968 (Box 27)
      - Birth Control: all the methods that work…and the ones that don't (Planned Parenthood of New York City, 1971) (Box 27)
      - Sam Leonard and Harold Hull, Sex and the g.c. student, undated [Greensboro College] (Box 27)
      - Gary Jones, Birth Control, Abortion and VD: A Guide for the University Student (Univ. of South Florida, 1971) (Box 27)
      - Venereal Disease, Abortion, Birth Control: A Guide for the tri-cities area, Union College Student Senate and Planned Parenthood League of Schenectady, NY, 1971 (Box 27)
      - Arthur M. Horowitz, everything you always wanted to know about birth control but were afraid to ask, CSU Student Health Service, undated (Box 27)
      - Ronald J. Pion et al., Now that you've delivered, Pfarrago Information Systems, 1972 (Box 27)
      - Hooked, USPHS, undated (Box 27)
      - The Boulder Birth Control Handbook, Birth Control Information Commission, Univ. of Colorado, 1970 (Box 27)
      - An Ounce of Prevention, Ad Hoc Committee for Contraception and Abortion Information, U of VA, undated (Box 27)
      - Medicine for the People, undated [Univ. of Alberta] (Box 27)
      - Nursing Outlook (Nov. 1970) (Box 27)
      - Special issue on Human Sexuality (Box 27)
    - Sex Education - Cartoons for [Removed from box 20] (Box 1)
- Accession, 2007 (2007-0043), 35 Boxes
  Addition (13,125 items, 21.0 linear feet) contains subject files that chronicle the history of the Crist Clinic from the opening of the clinic in 1973 to the early 21st century. The majority of the files contain Takey Crist's clippings on medical topics and issues relating to sex education and women's health care. Many files also refer to issues of significance for physicians running a private clinic.
  - Crist Clinic Subject Files Series
    - AASEC (Box 1)
    - Abortion, undated (Box 1)
    - Abortion 1970s (Box 1)
    - Abortion 1980s (Box 1)
    - Abortion 1990s (Box 1)
    - Abortion 2000s (Box 1)
    - Abortion: 1st Trimester (Box 1)
    - Abortion: 2nd trimester (Box 1)
    - Abortion: 2nd trimester abortion conference (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Anesthesia, pain control (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Attitudes of Medical Personnel (Box 1)
    - Abortion Services (Box 1)
    - Abortion, Commentary, NCMJ 1996 (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Complications (Box 1)
    - Abortion Correspondence (Box 1)
    - Abortion counseling (Box 1)
    - Abortion, Crist Clinic Survey Results in 1980 (Box 1)
    - Abortion Daily Tarheel (Box 1)
    - Abortion -- Don't Loose Your Right to Choose Cartoons (Box 1)
    - Abortion Ethics (Box 1)
    - Abortion, Fact Sheet, Parental Consent (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Fetal Indications (Box 1)
    - Abortion Fetal Pain (Box 1)
    - Abortion and the Greek Church (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Habitual (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Hypertonic Saline (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Induction (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Informed Consent (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Lawsuit Kenneth Edelin (Box 1)
    - Abortion: Lawsuit Jessie Floyd (Box 2)
    - Abortion: Lawsuit HEW (Box 2)
    - Abortion: Legal -- Roy Lucas (Box 2)
    - Abortion legislation (Box 2)
    - Abortion Legislation: Parental Consent (Box 2)
    - Abortion Legislation: pba (Box 2)
    - Abortion, medical - RU 486 (Box 2)
    - Abortion and Men (Box 2)
    - Abortion and Minors (Box 2)
    - Abortion: National Association of Abortion Services (Box 2)
    - Abortion: National Association of Reproductive Health Centers (Box 2)
    - Abortion: National Women's Health Organization (Box 2)
    - Abortion: North Carolina Coalition for Choice (Box 2)
    - Abortion: North Carolina Fight, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Abortion patients (Box 2)
    - Abortion Philosophy (Box 2)
    - Abortion: Planned Parenthood v. Casey (Box 2)
    - Abortion: psychiatric aspects (Box 2)
    - (Box 2)
    - Abortion and Religion (Box 3)
    - Abortion Rights Mobilization (Box 3)
    - Abortion Rules, NC Department of Human Resources, 12, Oct. 1993 (Box 3)
    - Abortion Statistics, NC and Onslow County (Box 3)
    - Abortion: Webster v. Reproductive Health Services (Box 3)
    - Ablation (Box 3)
    - ACLU (Box 3)
    - Acne (Box 3)
    - Acupuncture (Box 3)
    - Adolescent Depression (Box 3)
    - Adolescent Gynecology (Box 3)
    - Adolescent Health, Sexuality, and Parenting, Florida, 2nd Annual Conference on, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Adoption (Box 3)
    - Advertising (Box 3)
    - Advertising, Luke Management (Box 3)
    - AHEC Educational Program (Box 3)
    - AIDS (Box 3)
    - Alan Guttmacher Institute (Box 4)
    - Alcoholism (Box 4)
    - Alcohol and Pregnancy (Box 4)
    - Allergies (Gyn Patients) (Box 4)
    - Alzheimers (Box 4)
    - Amenorrhea (Box 4)
    - American Association of Planned Parenthood Physicians (Box 4)
    - American College of Obstetricians and Gynecologists (Box 4)
    - ACOG Manual of Standards in OB-GYN (Box 4)
    - ACOG Newsletter (Box 4)
    - ACOG Committee on Professional Personnel, 1972-1973 (Box 4)
    - ACOG Committee on Professional Personnel, 1973-1974 (Box 4)
    - American College of Surgeons (Box 4)
    - Americans for Religious Liberty (Box 4)
    - American Journal of Ob Gyn (Box 4)
    - American Way Press Clips (Box 4)
    - Amniocentesis (Box 5)
    - Amniotic Fluid (Box 5)
    - Anemia (Box 5)
    - Anencephalic fetus (Box 5)
    - Anesthesia and Analgesia (Box 5)
    - Anorexia Nervosa (Box 5)
    - Antibiotics (Box 5)
    - Antibiotics, Cefoxitin (Box 5)
    - Antibiotics, Mefoxin (Box 5)
    - Anticoagulants (Box 5)
    - Anticonvulsant Therapy (Box 5)
    - Aphrodisiac (Box 5)
    - Appendectomy (Box 5)
    - Appetite Suppressants (Box 5)
    - Articles -- Newspaper Clippings (Box 5)
    - Artificial Insemination (Box 5)
    - ARHP (Association of Reproductive Health Professionals) (Box 5)
    - Aspartame (Box 5)
    - Asthma (Box 5)
    - Author Information (Box 5)
    - Autotransfusion (Box 5)
    - "Baby Doe" Regulation (Box 5)
    - Bill Baird - Pro Choice League (Box 5)
    - Bells Palsy (Box 5)
    - Beta-Strep Infections (Box 5)
    - John Birch Society (Box 5)
    - Birth Defects (Box 5)
    - Birth Injuries (Box 5)
    - Birthing Center (Box 5)
    - Bleeding - abnormal vaginal (Box 6)
    - Bleeding - gastrointestinal (Box 6)
    - Bleeding -- Nosebleeds (Box 6)
    - Blood Clotting (Box 6)
    - Blood Disorders (Box 6)
    - Blood Transfusions (Box 6)
    - Brain (Box 6)
    - Breast (Box 6)
    - Breast - Diseases of the Breast (Box 6)
    - Breast Exams (Box 6)
    - Breast Feeding (Box 6)
    - Breast Implants (Box 6)
    - Breast - X-rays (Box 6)
    - Breech Presentation (Box 6)
    - Biofeedback (Box 6)
    - Bromides (Box 6)
    - Bronchitis (Box 6)
    - Bulimia (Box 6)
    - Caffeine (Box 6)
    - Calcium (Box 6)
    - Cancer (Box 6)
    - Cancer -- Breast (Box 6)
    - Cancer -- Cervix (Box 6)
    - Cancer -- Colon (Box 6)
    - Cancer -- Endometrium (Box 6)
    - Cancer -- Fallopian Tube (Box 7)
    - Cancer -- Female Genital Tract (Box 7)
    - Cancer -- Ovary (Box 7)
    - Cancer and Pregnancy (Box 7)
    - Cancer Screening (Box 7)
    - Cancer - Skin (Box 7)
    - Cancer -- Uterus (Box 7)
    - Cancer -- Vagina (Box 7)
    - Cancer -- Vulva (Box 7)
    - Capital Choice (Box 7)
    - Cardiopulmonary resuscitation (Box 7)
    - Cerebral Palsy (Box 7)
    - Cerebrovascular Diseases (Box 7)
    - Cervix (Box 7)
    - Cesarean-hysterectomy (Box 7)
    - Cesarean Section (Box 7)
    - Cesarean Section Study for Southern Illinois University (Box 7)
    - Child Abuse (Box 7)
    - Child Sexual Abuse (Box 7)
    - China (Box 8)
    - Cholesterol (Box 8)
    - Chronic Villous Biopsy, ECU and Crist Clinic (Box 8)
    - Christian OBGYN (Box 8)
    - Circumcision Female (Box 8)
    - Circumcision Male (Box 8)
    - Cocaine (Box 8)
    - Colostomy/Ileostomy (Box 8)
    - Colposcopy (Box 8)
    - Committee on Marriage Counseling and Family Life Education (Box 8)
    - Condoms (Box 8)
    - Contraceptive Failure (Box 8)
    - Contraceptives -- Dalkon Shield (Box 8)
    - Contraceptives, Depo-Provera (Box 8)
    - Contraceptives, Diaphragm (Box 8)
    - Contraceptives, IUD (Box 9)
    - Contraceptives, medical literature (Box 9)
    - Contraceptives, Norplant (Box 9)
    - Contraceptives -- Norplant: is it difficult to visualize, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Contraceptives, Oral - medical literature (Box 9)
    - Contraceptives, Oral -- Thromboembolic Phenomena (Box 9)
    - Contraceptives, popular press (Box 10)
    - Contraceptive Practice (Box 10)
    - Contraceptives, Teenagers (Box 10)
    - Contraceptives, Vaginal (Box 10)
    - Crist Clinic - Focus Newsletter (Box 10)
    - Crist Clinic Staff (Box 10)
    - Cryosurgery (Box 10)
    - Cystitis (Box 10)
    - Cytomegalovirus (Box 10)
    - Death (Box 10)
    - Dermatology (Box 10)
    - DES Syndrome (Box 10)
    - Diabetes (Box 10)
    - Diabetes Screening (Box 10)
    - Diarrhea (Box 10)
    - Dilation and Curettage (Box 10)
    - Dilation and Curettage Techniques (Box 10)
    - Doctor's Urgent Care Center (Box 10)
    - Domestic Violence (Box 10)
    - Domoso (Box 10)
    - Downs Syndrome (Box 10)
    - Drug Actions and Interactions (Box 10)
    - Drug Actions and Interactions in Pregnancy (Box 11)
    - Drug Addiction (Box 11)
    - Drug Addiction in Pregnancy (Box 11)
    - Drug Addiction, Teenagers (Box 11)
    - Drug Advisory Committee (Box 11)
    - Drugs, Pharmaceutical Services (Box 11)
    - Dysmenorrhea (Box 11)
    - East Carolina Medical School (Box 11)
    - East Carolina Medical School, OBGYN Dept. (Box 11)
    - [Ectopic Pregnancy] - removed folder, still at clinic (Box 11)
    - Edema (Box 11)
    - Education (Box 11)
    - Endocrinology (Box 11)
    - Endometriosis (Box 11)
    - Endometrium (Box 11)
    - Endorphins (Box 11)
    - Endovaginal Sonography (Box 11)
    - Environment and Disease (Box 11)
    - Epidurals (Box 11)
    - Epilepsy (Box 11)
    - Episiotomy (Box 11)
    - Estrogen (Box 12)
    - Estrogen Replacement Therapy (Box 12)
    - Euthanasia (Box 12)
    - Fallopian Tubes (Box 12)
    - Family Life Publications, Inc. (Box 12)
    - Family Planning, natural (Box 12)
    - Family Planning Services (Box 12)
    - Family Planning Services Carteret County, NC (Box 12)
    - Family Planning Services -- Health Department, Jacksonville, NC (Box 12)
    - Fern Pattern (Box 12)
    - Fertility - American Fertility Society (Box 12)
    - Fertility/Infertility (Box 13)
    - Fertility/Infertility - male (Box 13)
    - Fertility/Infertility - popular press (Box 13)
    - Fertility/Infertility, Dr. Talbert's Paper (Box 13)
    - Fetal Distress (Box 13)
    - Fetal Maturity (Box 13)
    - Fetal Monitor (Box 13)
    - Fetus (Box 13)
    - Fever (Box 13)
    - Fibroids (Box 13)
    - Fistulae (Box 13)
    - Fluid Therapy (Box 13)
    - Forceps (Box 13)
    - French Medical Student, Exchange Summer 1979 (Box 13)
    - Gallbladder Disease (Box 13)
    - Gastrointestinal Disorders (Box 13)
    - General Practice (Box 13)
    - Genetic Counseling (Box 14)
    - Geriatric Care (Box 14)
    - Grant Funding (Box 14)
    - Gynecologic Examination (Box 14)
    - Gyn Surgery (Box 14)
    - Hair (Box 14)
    - Harper & Row, Correspondence (Box 14)
    - Harper & Row, manuscript The Sex Scene (Box 14)
    - Headaches (Box 14)
    - Head Injuries (Box 14)
    - Health Care (Box 14)
    - Health Care Finder Program (Box 14)
    - Health Care for Minors (Box 14)
    - Health Educators (Box 14)
    - Health Policy (Box 14)
    - Heart Attack (Box 15)
    - Helicobacter Pylori (Box 15)
    - Helms, Jesse (Box 15)
    - Hemoperitoneum (Box 15)
    - Hemostasis (Box 15)
    - Hemorrhoids (Box 15)
    - Hepatitis (Box 15)
    - Dr. W. Hern (Box 15)
    - Hernia Repair (Box 15)
    - Hester, Lawrence (Box 15)
    - Histamine (Box 15)
    - Home Delivery (Box 15)
    - Homosexuality (Box 15)
    - Hormones (Box 15)
    - Hormone Replacement Therapy (Box 15)
    - Hospice Program (Box 15)
    - Human Manifesto (Box 15)
    - Hustler Magazine - Larry Flynt (Box 15)
    - Hydatidiform Mole (Box 15)
    - Hyperbaric Oxygen Therapy (Box 15)
    - Hypercalcemia (Box 15)
    - Hypertension (Box 15)
    - Hypoglycemia (Box 15)
    - Hyponatremia (Box 15)
    - Hypospadias (Box 15)
    - Hysterectomy (Box 15)
    - Hysterosalpingography (Box 16)
    - Hysteroscopy (Box 16)
    - Idiopathic Thrombocytopenia (Box 16)
    - Immunization (Box 16)
    - Impotence (Box 16)
    - Incest (Box 16)
    - Induction of Birth (Box 16)
    - Infant Death (Box 16)
    - Infant Mortality (Box 16)
    - Infections (Box 16)
    - Influenza (Box 16)
    - Insurance USF&G Fiasco (Box 16)
    - International College of Surgeons (Box 16)
    - Intrauterine Adhesions (Box 16)
    - Intrauterine Synechiae (Box 16)
    - Intravascular Clotting (Box 16)
    - In Vitro Fertilization (Box 16)
    - Iron (Box 16)
    - Irritable Bowel Syndrome (Box 16)
    - IV-Information (Box 16)
    - Jacksonville (Box 16)
    - Jaundice (Box 16)
    - Jet Lag (Box 16)
    - Job Offers (Box 16)
    - Job Offers, Macon, GA (Box 16)
    - Journal of Obstetrics, Gynecology, and Neonatal Nursing, correspondence (Box 16)
    - Juvenile Delinquency (Box 16)
    - Kawasaki Disease (Box 16)
    - Kidneys (Box 16)
    - Ku Klux Klan (Box 16)
    - Labor and Delivery (Box 16)
    - Lactation (Box 16)
    - Laminaria Tent (Box 16)
    - Laparoscopy (Box 16)
    - Laparoscopy Equipment -- ACMI (Box 16)
    - Laparoscopy Equipment - Cameron Miller (Box 16)
    - Laparoscopy Equipment -- Elmed (Box 16)
    - Laparoscopy Equipment -- Martin (Box 16)
    - Laparoscopy Equipment - Surgical Specialties Instrument (Box 17)
    - Laparoscopy Equipment - Wolf (Box 17)
    - Laparotomy (Box 17)
    - Laser Surgery (Box 17)
    - Law and Medicine (Box 17)
    - Learning Disabilities (Box 17)
    - Leg Cramps (Box 17)
    - Lice (Box 17)
    - Liver (Box 17)
    - Lupus (Box 17)
    - Luteal Phase Defects (Box 17)
    - Lyme Disease (Box 17)
    - Magnesium (Box 17)
    - Malaria (Box 17)
    - Malpractice (Box 17)
    - Mammary Augmentation (Box 17)
    - Mammogram (Box 17)
    - Mammography Equipment (Box 17)
    - Marijuana (Box 17)
    - Marriage (Box 17)
    - Maternal Mortality (Box 17)
    - Measles (Box 17)
    - Media (Box 17)
    - Medicaid reimbursement South Carolina, correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 17)
    - Medical Alumni Bulletin, Write-up 1978 (Box 17)
    - Medical Assistant (Box 17)
    - Medical Assistant Student Program, James Sprunt Institute (Box 17)
    - Medical Education (Box 17)
    - Medical Records (Box 17)
    - Medical Students for Choice (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1973, Jan. 30-Feb. 2, Columbia Conference, Family Planning Patient Education (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1973, March 9-10, Norfolk, VA, Teenage Conference (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1973, May 19, Film Panel, Key Biscayne, FL (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1973, Oct. 21-25, ACOG District IV (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1974, Sept. 20-22, Robert A. Ross Society, Wrightsville Beach, N.C. (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1974, Oct. 24, ACOG, Miami Beach, FL (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1975, March 14-16, National Medicolegal Symposium, Las Vegas (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1975, Nov. 5, Health Care Report, BCBS, Kinston, NC (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1975, Nov. 12-14, ACOG Postgraduate Course, Las Vegas (Box 17)
    - Meeting - 1976, Aug. 9-12, International Symposium on Sex Education and Therapy, Stockholm, Sweden (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1976, Sept. 23-26, Robert A. Ross Society, Daytona Beach, FL (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1976, Sept. 30-Oct. 2, Update'76, ACOG and NY Medical College (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1977, Oct. 11-15, PPFA Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1978, April 27-30, North Carolina Obstetrical and Gynecological Society, Southern Pines, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1978, Sept. 24-26, National Abortion Federation Annual Meeting, San Francisco (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1978, Sept. 28-Oct. 1, Robert A. Ross Obstetrical and Gynecological Society, Annual Meeting (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1981, Feb. 6, Conference for Present and Future Medical Leaders, Raleigh, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1982, March 20-21, 15th Annual Postgraduate Course, American Fertility Society (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1983, Oct. 27, Planned Parenthood, Charlotte, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1984, Feb. 9-11, ACOG 1984 Postgraduate Course, Tarpon Springs, FL (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1984, April 6-7, 20 year reunion Class of 1964 (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1985, March 16, 20 Year Reunion Class of 1965 (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1986, March 10, NARAL Tribute to Providers, Washington DC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1986, May 1-4, NC Ob-Gyn Society, Southern Pines, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1986, Sept. 18-21, Robert A. Ross Society, Chapel Hill, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1987, April 30 to May 3, NC Obstetrical and Gynecological Society, Southern Pines, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1987, Aug. 14-16, Primary Care of the Female Patient, Cont. Ed., Virginia Beach, VA (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1987, Sept. 17-20, Robert A. Ross Society, Winston Salem, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1988, March 7-12, Wyeth-Ayerst Laboratories Medical Symposium, Vienna, Austria (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1988, April 29-30, ACOG North Carolina Section Meeting, Chapel Hill, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1988, June 27-29, Anglo-American Update in Obstetrics and Gynecology, Royal Society of (Box 18)
    - Medicine, London Meeting - 1988, Aug. 5-7, Robert A. Ross Medical Society, Asheville, NC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1988, Sept. 29-30, Surgery Course, Columbia Univ., NYC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1989, March 12-13, Albert Einstein College of Medicine, Searle & Co., NYC (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1989, Oct. 26-27, Emory School of Medicine, Atlanta, GA (Box 18)
    - Meeting - 1990, April 19-22, Ortho Meeting, Acapulco, Mexico (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1990, April 20-22, NC Obstetrical and Gynecological Society, Pinehurst, NC (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1990, April 26, Controversies and Critical Issues in Obstetrics, ECU (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1990, May 8, Hulka Meeting (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1990, Oct. 4-7, Robert A. Ross Society, Chapel Hill, NC (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1991, Nov. 2-5, ACOG District IV Meeting, Charleston, SC (Box 19)
    - Meeting - 1992, Feb. 5, Raleigh Women's Health Organization (Box 19)